{
    "subject": "resource/Tribalistas",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Brazil",
    "human_readable": "Tribalistas is from Brazil.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.887887179851532,
            "question": "Is Tribalistas a Brazilian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7676714658737183,
            "question": "Where is Tribalistas from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.650111973285675,
            "question": "Where do Tribalistas originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334553956985474,
            "question": "What country are Tribalistas associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6104636788368225,
            "question": "Who are some members of Tribalistas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025383472442627,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Tribalistas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41515275835990906,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Tribalistas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2708932161331177,
            "question": "Are Tribalistas known for their music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1807805597782135,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by Tribalistas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1530163586139679,
            "question": "What genre of music does Tribalistas play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tribalistas is from Brazil.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8605_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by Tribalistas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8605_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Tribalistas known for their music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8605_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Tribalistas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8605_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8605_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Tribalistas is from Brazil\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Tribalistas is a Brazilian supergroup, consists of Brazilian artists, and released an album in Brazil in 2002. The information supports the statement that Tribalistas is indeed from Brazil."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that Tribalistas is a Brazilian musical group, which supports the statement that they are from Brazil."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}